{
	"Questions" : {
	  "1" : {
	    "question" : "One MB is equal to",
		"option1" : "1024 Byte",
		"option2" : "1024 KB",
		"option3" : "1000 KB",
		"option4" : "1024 GB",
		"answer" : "1024 KB"
	  },
	  "2" : {
	    "question" : "On which later TCP is used?",
		"option1" : "Session layer",
		"option2" : "Transport layer",
		"option3" : "Network layer",
		"option4" : "Application layer",
		"answer" : "Transport layer"
	  },
	  "3" : {
	    "question" : "Basic architecture of computer was developed by",
		"option1" : "John Von Neumann",
		"option2" : "Charles Babbage",
		"option3" : "Blaise Pascal",
		"option4" : "Garden Moore",
		"answer" : "John Von Neumann"
	  },
	  "4" : {
	    "question" : "In how many generations a computer can be classified?",
		"option1" : "3",
		"option2" : "4",
		"option3" : "5",
		"option4" : "6",
		"answer" : "5"
	  },
	  "5" : {
	    "question" : "Fifth generation computers are based on",
		"option1" : "Artificial intelligence",
		"option2" : "Programming intelligence",
		"option3" : "System knowledge",
		"option4" : "VVLSI",
		"answer" : "Artificial intelligence"
	  },
	  "6" : {
	    "question" : "GUI stands for",
		"option1" : "Graph Use Interface",
		"option2" : "Graphical User Interface",
		"option3" : "Graphical Unique Interface",
		"option4" : "None of these",
		"answer" : "Graphical User Interface"
	  },
	  "7" : {
	    "question" : "Time during which a job is proccessed by the computer is",
		"option1" : "Execution time",
		"option2" : "Delay time",
		"option3" : "Real time",
		"option4" : "Waiting time",
		"answer" : "Waiting time"
	  },
	  "8" : {
	    "question" : "An error is also known as",
		"option1" : "Debug",
		"option2" : "Bug",
		"option3" : "Cursor",
		"option4" : "Icon",
		"answer" : "Bug"
	  },
	  "9" : {
	    "question" : "Microsoft Word is an example of",
		"option1" : "an operating system",
		"option2" : "processing device",
		"option3" : "application software",
		"option4" : "an input device",
		"answer" : "application software"
	  },
	  "10" : {
	    "question" : "Who invented the super computer?",
		"option1" : "PT Fransworth",
		"option2" : "JH Van Tassell",
		"option3" : "Charles Ginsberg",
		"option4" : "Charles Babbage",
		"answer" : "JH Van Tassell"
	  }
	}
}